Herold Levente Kiraly

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Profile

I have always been fascinated by technology and have decided to pursue a career as a software engineer, something I have dabbled in as a hobby in the past. I have spent the past couple of years working in B2C sales and business management, where I have gained experience working directly with clients to ensure that jobs were completed on time and to their standards. In early 2021, I decided to take a break for a career change and spent the past two years learning and exploring software development.

Employment History

Frontend Web Developer, Freelance, New York City Metropolitan Area

MAY 2022 - PRESENT

- Creating responsive modern web applications for individuals and small business, using the latest web stack of technologies/frameworks.
- Skills: HTML5 · Flask · MySQL · SASS · Python (Programming Language) · React.js · JavaScript · Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)

Career Transition, Career Break, New York

FEBRUARY 2021 - PRESENT

Learning a variety of programming languages mainly focusing on the Frontend Stacks and the creation of user interfaces/web and app design.

Company Director, Reno Kings LLC, Bergen County, New Jersey, USA

MARCH 2019 - FEBRUARY 2021

- Operational director of the company, managed company budget and finances, lead a small team and also direct communication with clients.
- **Skills:** Team Management · Finance · Management · Direct Sales · Team Leadership

Job Manager, Glower Designs & Construction, Inc., New York City

JANUARY 2018 — JANUARY 2019

- Managed internal business operations, Client communication, On-site job management, Product/Service Sales.
- Skills: Client Relations · Business · Business Strategy · Sales

Salesperson, PHP Agency, Inc., United States

APRIL 2017 - JANUARY 2018

- Direct on phone sales with potential prospects, In person sales and in house team meetings. Which occasionally consisted of presentations.
- Skills: Presentation Skills Networking Communication Marketing Sales

Ecommerce Marketing Manager, Nperor LLC, New York City

MARCH 2017 - JANUARY 2018

- Brought in sales through the creation of sales funnels and professional copy writing
- Skills: Marketing Strategy · E-Commerce · Lead Generation · Email Marketing
 Product Research

Education

Front End Engineer, Codecademy

Computer Science (CS50x), Harvard University

Technology (CS50T), Harvard University

Details

Albrightsville, PA United States (201) 381-1996 kiraly-h@protonmail.com

Links

Portfolio Website: https://heroldkiraly.github.io/ Github:

https://github.com/HeroldKiraly

Skills

HTML & CSS JavaScript React

MySQL Python

Git C lang

Mobile First Workflow

Webpack

Hobbies

Skiing, Traveling, Exploring, Reading, Car Enthusiast

Languages

English

Hungarian